# — EDEH JOHNPAUL —

# **CONTACT**



07042906747



☑ edehjohnpaul@gmail.com



edehjohnpaul.com

# **PROFILE**

Hi, I'm a software developer who is passionate about learning new technologies and also a quick learner, my tools are MongoDB, react, node, express, TailwindCSS, and Nextjs, I also love building web solutions with modern tools, I have 2 years experience in web development

#### SKILLS

- WEB DEVELOPMENT
- HTML/CSS/TAILWINDCSS
- **MONGODB**
- **EXPRESS/NODEJS**
- REACTJS
- **NEXTJS**

# **EDUCATION**

# NNAMDI AZIKIWE UNIVERSITY

2020- TO DATE

B.eng

Currently studying Electronics and Computer Engineering

#### **CKC ONITSHA**

2012-2018

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### **ECE-NAU**

2022- present

Full stack developer

#### EE MADE MY LIFE PRODUCTION

FEBRUARY, 2021-2023

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

- Produced websites compatible with multiple browsers.
- Performed user experience quality assurance testing to identify and remedy shortcomings.
- Designed and updated layouts to meet usability and performance requirements. Coded using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to develop features for both mobile and desktop platforms.
- Improved tools to boost user interaction and deliver design versatility.

# **INTEREST**

Web3, Blockchain, AI, Playing games, and watching movies

#### REFERENCES

**Udemgba Ferdinand**, Software Developer, ECE-NAU